var quiz = [
  {
    question: "What is the most common contaminant found in the ocean?",
    answer: "Plastic",
    success_message: "",
    failed_message: ""
  },
  {
    question: "By what year will plastic outnumber the fish in the ocean",
    choices: ["2025","2050", "2075", "Never"],
    answer: 1,
    success_message: "",
    failed_message: ""
  },
  {
    question: "How many percent of seabirds eat plastic on a regular basis ?",
    choices: ["10%", "50%", "90%"]
    answer: 2,
    success_message: "Yes, the numbers are stagerring. ",
    failed_message: "N"
  },
  {
    question: "The accumulation of plastic in the ocean is so overwhelming that it has produced a seventh continent? What is its size?",
    choices: ["1/6th the size of France", "the size of France", "6 times the size of France"],
    answer: 2,
    success_message:"Indeed that represents 3,5 square kilometers",
    failed_message: "N"
  },
    {
    question: "In which year was this Great Pacific Garbage Patch found",
    answer: "1997",
    success_message: "Y",
    failed_message: "N"
  }
   {
    question: "For how many per cent does land-based pollution account for marine pollution",
    choices: ["50%", "80%", "100%"],
    answer: 1,
    success_message: "Y",
    failed_message: "N"
  },  
  {
    question: "Boyan Slat is the founder of the project Ocean Cleanup. What is his project about?",
    answer: ["Install floating traps to recover plastic in the ocean", "Commercialise a new kind of plastic that also serve as food for marine species", "Invent a liquid solution that will decompose plastic in safe bits"]
    success_message: "Y",
    failed_message: "N"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the most commonly recovered item in the annual International Cleanup event?",
    answer: "Cigarette Butt",
    success_message: "Y",
    failed_message: "N"
  },
    {
    question: "How much liter of water can one cigarette butt pollute if thrown into",
    answer: ["50 litres", "500 litres", "5000 liters"]
    success_message: "Y",
    failed_message: "N"
  }
  {
    question: "In which month the next ocean clean up day takes place?",
    answer: "September",
    success_message: "Exactly ! It takes places every year on the third saturday in September. So for 2018, it will happen on the 15th. Will you participate?",
    failed_message: "Actually, It takes places every year on the third saturday in September. So for 2018, it will happen on the 15th. Will you participate ?"
  }
];